(Leonard:)I'm sorry,
we cannot do this without Wolowitz.
(Leonard:)We can't order Chinese food
without Wolowitz?
(Sheldon:)Let me walk you through it.
Our standard order is,
the steamed dumpling appetizer...
...General Tso's chicken,
beef with broccoli...
(Sheldon:)...shrimp with lobster sauce,
and vegetable lo mein.
(Sheldon:)Do you see the problem?
(Leonard:)I see a problem.
(Sheldon:)Our entire order is predicated
on four dumplings and four entrées...
...divided amongst four people.
So we'll just order three entrées.
Fine. What do you wanna eliminate?
- And who gets the extra dumpling?
- We could cut it into thirds.
Then it's no longer a dumpling.
(Sheldon:)Once you cut it open, it is, at best,
a very small open-faced sandwich.
(Waiter:)Hi, fellas.
(Waiter:)Oh. Where's your annoying little friend
who thinks he speaks Mandarin?
(Sheldon:)He's putting his needs
ahead of the collective good.
(Sheldon:)Where he comes from,
that's punishable by death.
(Waiter:)I come from Sacramento.